http://www.bristolfarm.com.au/pages/our-privacy-policy

PLEASE INDICATE YOUR DATE OF BIRTH.
1910
SORRY, AS YOU ARE NOT OF LEGAL AGE, WE CANNOT WELCOME YOU TO OUR SITE.
Our Privacy Policy
Bristol Farm Wines is committed to providing quality services to you and this policy outlines our ongoing obligations to you in respect of how we manage your Personal Information.
What is Personal Information and why do we collect it?
Personal Information is information or an opinion that identifies an individual. Examples of Personal Information we collect include: names, addresses, email addresses, phone and facsimile numbers.
This Personal Information is obtained in many ways including correspondence, by telephone,  facsimile, by email, via our website, from your website, from media and publications, from other publicly available sources, from cookies and from third parties. We don’t guarantee website links or policy of authorised third parties.
We collect your Personal Information for the primary purpose of providing our services to you, providing information to our customers and marketing. We may also use your Personal Information for secondary purposes closely related to the primary purpose, in circumstances where you would reasonably expect such use or disclosure. You may unsubscribe from our mailing/marketing lists at any time by contacting us in writing.
When we collect Personal Information we will, where appropriate and where possible, explain to you why we are collecting the information and how we plan to use it.
Third Parties
Where reasonable and practicable to do so, we will collect your Personal Information only from you. However, in some circumstances we may be provided with information by third parties. In such a case we will take reasonable steps to ensure that you are made aware of the information provided to us by the third party.
We will not provide your Personal Information to any unauthorised third party.
Disclosure of Personal Information
Your Personal Information may be disclosed in a number of circumstances including the following:
Third parties where you consent to the use or disclosure; and
Where required or authorised by law.
Security of Personal Information
When purchasing via our website your financial details are processed through a secure server using SSL ( secure sockets layer ) encryption technology.
Your Personal Information is stored in a manner that reasonably protects it from misuse and loss and from unauthorized access, modification or disclosure.
When your Personal Information is no longer needed for the purpose for which it was obtained, we will take reasonable steps to destroy or permanently de-identify your Personal Information. However, most of the Personal Information is or will be stored in customer files which will be kept by us for a minimum of 7 years.
Access to your Personal Information
You may access the Personal Information we hold about you and to update and/or correct it, subject to certain exceptions. If you wish to access your Personal Information, please contact us in writing.
Bristol Farm Wines will not charge any fee for your access request, but may charge an administrative fee for providing a copy of your Personal Information.
In order to protect your Personal Information we may require identification from you before releasing the requested information.
Cookies
Cookies are small text files that are stored by the browser on your computer or mobile device. They allow websites to store things like user preferences. You can think of cookies as providing a “memory “  for the website so that it can recognise you when you return and can respond accordingly.
We use cookies for a variety of purposes such as  :
identifying you when you sign in to our site
keeping track of your preferences
preventing fraudulent activities
Should you wish to do so it is usually possible to stop your browser accepting cookies or to stop it accepting cookies from a particular website.
Email Lists
Subscribers can join our mailing list to receive our newsletter, new releases, blog and updates. You may unsubscribe at any time.
Maintaining the Quality of your Personal Information
It is important to us that your Personal Information is up to date. We will take reasonable steps to make sure that your Personal Information is accurate, complete and up-to-date. If you find that the information we have is not up to date or is inaccurate, please advise us as soon as practicable so we can update our records and ensure we can continue to provide quality services to you.
Policy Updates
This Policy may change from time to time and is available on our website.
Privacy Policy Complaints and Enquiries
If you have any queries or complaints about our Privacy Policy please contact us at:
info@bristolfarm.com.au
PO Box 1292, Hawksburn 3142, Australia
+61 419 599 209
If you are shipping an item over $75, you should consider using a trackable shipping service or purchasing shipping insurance. We don’t guarantee that we will receive your returned item.
Join The Bristol Farm Newsletter
Submit
Stay up to date with the latest news and releases from Bristol Farm Wine
Read our Privacy Policy and our Terms and Conditions.
Website By Programmable Soda
Liquor Licence 36062092
WARNING
Under the Liquor Control Reform Act 1998 it is an offence
To supply alcohol to a person under the age of 18 years (Penalty
exceeds $17,000)
For a person under the age of 18 years to purchase or receive liquor. (Penalty exceeds $500)
